## **CALEB ADRIAN**

208-890-7995

http://calebadrian.github.io

calebadrian1847@gmail.com

#### **PROFILE**

Driven and focused team member with full stack development skills. Able to solve complex problems both individually as well as in a team to find solutions and resolve them in the best and most efficient way possible. Previously attended school at University of Idaho where I took my first programming course that sparked my interest in web development. I transferred from University of Idaho down to Boise State University to enroll in their computer science program. While attending I found Boise CodeWorks and decided that I would like to get some real experience under my belt as well as continue my education part-time while working following my graduation from Boise CodeWorks.

#### **SKILLS**

HTML5
JavaScript
CSS3
NodeJS
Chai/Mocha
Sass
Bootstrap
VueJS
Git
MySQL

### **EXPERIENCE**

### **FULL STACK DEVELOPMENT STUDENT, BOISE CODEWORKS**

01/2018-04/2018

- Utilized proper coding structure utilizing proper tags and comments in order to ensure readable and reusable code for the future
- Practiced both use and writing RESTful API structure to effectively create websites using and storing data in real time
- Experienced large data sets like the NFL and iTunes APIs to be able to handle the volume of data created in the real world
- Used frameworks such as Vue and Node to quickly and efficiently create and add features to websites to improve user experience
- · Worked in individual, partner programming, and group work to be able to work in any professional work environment
- Acquired great problem solving skills due to many challenges set forth that require unique thinking in order to come to a solution
- Integrated user authentication in to many websites built throughout the course making integration into any website seamless

### **SALES MANAGER**, SEARS OUTLET

2/2017-01/2018

- Promoted from sales associate due to being a consistent top performer in sales as well as consistently going above and beyond
- Responsible for contacting upper management on a day to day basis to ensure that every customer was satisfied to my best ability
- Proper training of the sales staff including product knowledge and operations as well as strategies in order to be successful in sales
- Meeting with sales staff to ensure that weekly and monthly goals were being hit and making any adjustments where needed

SALES ASSOCIATE 08/2016-02/2017

- Responsible for greeting customers and helping them find the correct merchandise based on all their requirements
- Proper use of the point of sale system to ensure a quick, efficient, and accurate sale to maximize customer satisfaction
- · Strategy and problem solving to read customers to and make the correct decision to make that customers experience better

# **WAREHOUSE ASSOCIATE** 07/2015-08/2016

- Responsible for proper handling of merchandise from the sales floor to the warehouse as well as loading merchandise
- Worked in a team setting to unload and check in shipments quickly to provide our customers the best merchandise

## **EDUCATION**

BOISE STATE UNIVERSITY, BOISE, ID — COMPUTER SCIENCE, 2019 (IN PROGRESS) BOISE CODEWORKS, BOISE, ID - FULL STACK DEVELOPMENT, 2018 UNIVERSITY OF IDAHO, MOSCOW, ID — CHEMICAL ENGINEERING, 2014(INCOMPLETE) BETA THETA PI SCHOLARSHIP CHAIR — 2011 — 2012 BETA THETA PI TREASURER FOR PLEDGE CLASS OF 2009 — 2009 - 2010 ACTIVE BETA THETA PI MEMBER